<resources>
    <string name="s_project_name">Karya</string>
    <string name="s_no_internet_or_server_down">We are not able to reach our server. Please ensure you have internet turned on.</string>
    <string name="s_click_to_retry">Click this button to retry</string>
    <string name="s_unknown_error">Unknown error occurred. Please close the application and open again. If error persists, contact your project coordinator</string>
    <string name="s_salutation">Hi</string>
    <string name="s_show_app_in_language">Show the app in English</string>
    <string name="s_prompt_for_language_select">To show app in English, press here</string>
    <string name="s_fetching_values_for_language">Getting all necessary data to display the app in English</string>
    <string name="s_consent_form_title">Consent Form</string>
    <string name="s_access_code_title">Enter Access Code</string>
    <string name="s_otp_title">Enter OTP</string>
    <string name="s_phone_number_title">Enter Phone Number</string>
    <string name="s_age_title">Select Age Group</string>
    <string name="s_gender_title">Select Gender</string>
    <string name="s_profile_pic_title">Select Profile Picture</string>
    <string name="s_dashboard_title">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="s_consent_form_agree">I agree</string>
    <string name="s_consent_form_disagree">No. I do not want to participate</string>
    <string name="s_consent_form_text">
        <![CDATA[
        <h5>Karya Participation Consent Form</h5>
<p>
  Thank you for your participation on the Karya platform. This document
  describes the goals of the platform and the various steps involved in your
  participation. You have no obligation to participate. You may end your
  participation at any time.
</p>
<h5>Purpose of the Platform</h5>
<p>
  The goal of the platform is to offer paid digital work to various users.
  Through the Karya smartphone app, you can get access to simple tasks that can
  be completed on your smartphone. You will get paid for all the correctly
  completed tasks. The type of task assigned to you will depend on the specific
  study you are participating in. For instance, a task may require you to record
  yourself speaking out a sentence. Regardless, the Karya app will provide you
  clear instructions on how to complete each task in your regional language. The
  app will also inform you how much you will be paid if you complete the task
  correctly. You can withdraw from participation at any time, and you will be
  paid for the tasks you have completed till that point.
</p>
<h5>Procedure</h5>
<ol>
  <li>
    To begin, you will be introduced to the Project Coordinator for your
    location. This person will be your point of contact for help related to the
    project.
  </li>
  <li>
    Your project coordinator will provide you with instructions and if
    necessary, help you to download and install the “Karya” mobile application
    on your smartphone.
  </li>
  <li>
    Your project coordinator will give you a “16-digit Access Code”. You need to
    enter the code during the registration process. Each access code can be used
    only once. Therefore, do not share the access code with anyone else.
  </li>
  <li>
    The registration process may require you to sign-in with your phone number.
    This information will be used to identify you on the platform when you close
    the application and open it again.
  </li>
  <li>
    In addition, we will also collect some demographic information about you,
    e.g., your age range, gender, education level, etc.
  </li>
  <li>
    The app will also ask you to choose a profile picture. This picture will
    only be used for display in the application and will not be stored in our
    platform.
  </li>
  <li>
    To receive tasks on our platform, the app must “sync” with our server. This
    operation will submit all the tasks you have completed on our platform to
    the server and receive any new tasks. After registration, the app will
    automatically sync with our server. You can trigger subsequent syncs by
    clicking on the sync button in the app.
  </li>
  <li>
    In the main app screen (dashboard), you will be presented with a list of
    different type of tasks assigned to you, along with information on each type
    of task: number of tasks assigned, number of tasks completed, number of
    tasks submitted, etc. For each type of task, the app will provide detailed
    instructions on how you must complete the task, and how much you will be
    paid if you complete the task correctly. Please pay attention to these
    instructions before proceeding with the tasks.
  </li>
  <li>
    At the end of your participation, we request you to delete the application
    from your phone. Should you want, your project coordinator will aid you in
    installing, configuring, and deleting the application.
  </li>
  <li>
    After the end of the study, we may request a short interview with you to
    gather your feedback and understand your experience of using our platform.
  </li>
</ol>
<h5>Risks and Benefits</h5>
<ol>
  <li>
    This platform only offers supplemental work. As a result, we have a limited
    number of tasks available. Do not let your participation in our platform
    interfere with your current work. Your participation will only require upto
    one to two hours of your time every day.
  </li>
  <li>
    We recommend doing the provided work in a patient manner. This will allow
    you to submit more accurate responses and will also make sure you don’t
    spend too much time on the smartphone. Spending too much time on a
    smartphone could be bad for your eyes and may affect your social life. We
    recommend not working for more than 2 hours a day.
  </li>
  <li>
    If we lend you a smartphone to participate (as part of a research study), we
    trust you to use the provided smartphone responsibly. If you have not used a
    smartphone before, it can be overwhelming. We are happy to help you in any
    and every way possible. You can contact us via your project coordinator.
  </li>
</ol>
<h5>Personal Information</h5>
<p>
  Any personal information we collect during the study will only be used to
  identify you during the duration of the study. We will delete all personal
  information as soon as the study is over. We will not share your personal
  information with anyone. However, we may use pictures from the study in
  presentations or posters without identifying specific individuals. We will
  request your permission before taking pictures and obtain your permission to
  use those pictures in our presentations or posters. Not providing consent for
  taking pictures will not disqualify you from participating in the study. For
  additional information or concerns about how Microsoft handles your personal
  information, please see the Microsoft Privacy Statement,
  https://go.microsoft.com/fwlink/?LinkId=521839
</p>
<h5>Payment for Participation</h5>
<p>
  You will be paid for all correctly completed tasks on the platform. The app or
  your porject coordinator will also provide you feedback on how well you are
  performing on the platform so that you can improve your responses for future
  tasks. We will work with you and your project coordinator to identify the best
  mode of payment. We will collect and store your payment information for the
  duration of the study. We will pay you periodically for all your tasks that
  have undergone quality verification. We will delete all payment information as
  soon as your participation is completed. Please contact your project
  coordinator if you have any queries regarding payments.
</p>
<h5>Dataset Collected from the Study</h5>
<p>
  We will use the dataset collected as part of your responses to different tasks
  for further research and will aim to release them publicly for research
  purposes. Most datasets will contain only text or audio data that is not
  associated with personally identifiable information. In situations where a
  dataset does contain personally identifiable information (e.g., video), we
  will obtain explicit consent from you before providing such a task. If you
  have any questions regarding how the dataset will be used, please feel free to
  ask us through your project coordinator or using the phone number provided
  below.
</p>
<h5>Contact Information</h5>
<p>
  Should you have any questions concerning the project, you can contact Vivek
  Seshadri by phone at 0000000000. Should you have any questions about your
  rights as a research subject, please report your concern via email to
  Microsoft Research Ethics Program Feedback: MSRStudyfeedback@microsoft.com. In
  case you do not have access to email, you can contact your project
  coordinator, and have her relay your concerns.
</p>
<h5>Consent</h5>
<p>
  By clicking “I agree” below, you confirm that the goals and the procedure for
  participation on the platform was explained to you, you had a chance to ask
  questions before beginning your participation, and all your questions were
  answered satisfactorily. By clicking “I agree” below, you voluntarily consent
  to participate, and you do not give up any legal rights you have as a study
  participant. On behalf of Karya Inc, we thank you for your contribution and
  look forward to your participation. Do you understand and consent to these
  terms?
</p>
 ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="s_consent_form_summary">Summary of the consent form</string>
    <string name="s_access_code_prompt">You should have received a 8-digit access code from your
        teacher. Please enter that access code below.</string>
    <string name="s_invalid_creation_code">You have entered an invalid creation code.</string>
    <string name="s_creation_code_already_used">The creation code you have entered is already
        used. Please contact your teacher.</string>
    <string name="s_phone_number_prompt">To use Karya, you need to register with our application using your phone number. Please enter your phone number below.</string>
    <string name="s_sending_otp">Sending OTP to your phone</string>
    <string name="s_unable_to_send_otp">We were unable to send OTP to your number. Please try again later.</string>
    <string name="s_otp_prompt">We have sent you a 6-digit OTP via SMS. Please enter that OTP below</string>
    <string name="s_invalid_otp">You have entered an invalid OTP</string>
    <string name="s_resend_otp">Resend OTP</string>
    <string name="s_profile_picture_prompt">Please click your profile picture. You can skip this step if you do not want a profile picture</string>
    <string name="s_gender_prompt">Please choose your gender</string>
    <string name="s_male">Male</string>
    <string name="s_female">Female</string>
    <string name="s_age_prompt">Please enter your year of birth</string>
    <string name="s_years">years</string>
    <string name="s_registering_worker">Registering worker with the server</string>
    <string name="s_phone_number_already_used">Your phone number is already registered. Please try with another phone number.</string>
    <!-- TODO: update tick and cross with more suitable words -->
    <string name="s_skill_question_description">We have three questions about your skills in English. For each question, please click tick for yes, and cross for no.</string>
    <string name="s_read_skill_question">Can you read in English?</string>
    <string name="s_speak_skill_question">Can you speak in English?</string>
    <string name="s_type_skill_question">Can you type in English?</string>
    <string name="s_registering_skill">Registering new skill for worker</string>
    <string name="s_failed_to_register_skill">Failed to register new skill for worker</string>
    <string name="s_other_language_selection">If you know any other language, please select that language below</string>
    <string name="s_uploading_files">Uploading files to the box</string>
    <string name="s_send_updates">Sending updates to the box</string>
    <string name="s_receive_updates">Receiving updates from the box</string>
    <string name="s_downloading_files">Downloading files from the box</string>
    <string name="s_get_new_tasks"> Get new homework</string>
    <string name="s_submit_completed_tasks">Submit completed homework</string>
    <string name="s_update_verified_tasks">Update graded homework</string>
    <string name="s_update_earning"></string>
    <string name="s_tasks_available">sentences not attempted</string>
    <string name="s_tasks_completed">sentences completed</string>
    <string name="s_tasks_skipped">sentences skipped</string>
    <string name="s_tasks_submitted">sentences submitted</string>
    <string name="s_tasks_verified">sentences graded</string>
    <string name="s_update_app_language">Change the App Language</string>
    <string name="s_update_skills">Update Language Skills</string>
    <string name="s_sync_prompt_message">You have completed sentences that can be submitted to the
        server. Do you want to submit the sentences now?</string>
    <string name="s_yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="s_no">No</string>
    <string name="s_speech_scenario_name">Speech-data Collection</string>
    <string name="s_speech_scenario_description">This task consists of a set of sentences. The worker is expected to record themselves reading out each sentence, one sentence at a time</string>
    <string name="s_story_scenario_name">Group Speech-data Collection</string>
    <string name="s_story_scenario_description">This task consists of a set of stories. The worker is expected to record themselves reading out each story, one sentence at a time</string>
    <string name="s_recording_scenario_name">Verification of Speech Data Recordings</string>
    <string name="s_recording_scenario_description">This task consists of a set of recordings. The worker is expected to verify the given recording and text.</string>
    <string name="s_record_sentence">You have to record yourself speaking out this sentence</string>
    <string name="s_record_action">To start recording, press this button. It will turn red indicating that the recording has started.</string>
    <string name="s_stop_action">Once you are done recording, press this button again to stop the recording</string>
    <string name="s_listen_action"> The app will play back the recorded audio. Listen to it carefully to ensure it is correct and that there is no other background voice.</string>
    <string name="s_rerecord_action">If your recording is not correct, you can record again using the record button.</string>
    <string name="s_next_action">If you are happy with the recording, you can press this button to go to the next sentence.</string>
    <string name="s_previous_action"> You can press this button to go to the previous sentence.</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="transliteration_hint">Start Typing…</string>
    <string name="text_transliteration_desc">Please transliterate the following word from English to Hindi</string>
    <string name="alphanumericString">abcdefghijklmnopqrstuvwxyz</string>

    <string name="video_record_button">I Understand and start recording</string>
    <string name="record_preview_message">The preview of the recording would appear here</string>
    <string name="dialogTitle">Skip sentence or record it later?</string>
    <string name="dialogMessage">Do you want to skip this sentence or record it later? Skipped sentences cannot be attempted again.</string>
</resources>
