<resources>
    <string name="language_name">EN</string>

    <!-- Errors -->
    <string name="unknown_error">Some unknown error occurred. Please contact your coordinator.</string>
    <string name="invalid_access_code">The access code you have entered is not valid. Please contact your coordinator.</string>
    <string name="access_code">Access Code</string>

    <!-- Consent Form Page -->
    <string name="consent_form_title">Consent Form</string>
    <string name="consent_form_agree">Agree</string>
    <string name="consent_form_disagree">I do not want to participate</string>
    <string name="consent_form_text">
        <![CDATA[
<h5>Karya Participation Consent Form</h5>
<p>
  Thank you for your participation on the Karya platform. This document
  describes the goals of the platform and the various steps involved in your
  participation. You have no obligation to participate. You may end your
  participation at any time.
</p>
<h5>Purpose of the Platform</h5>
<p>
  The goal of the platform is to offer paid digital work to various users.
  Through the Karya smartphone app, you can get access to simple tasks that can
  be completed on your smartphone. You will get paid for all the correctly
  completed tasks. The type of task assigned to you will depend on the specific
  study you are participating in. For instance, a task may require you to record
  yourself speaking out a sentence. Regardless, the Karya app will provide you
  clear instructions on how to complete each task in your regional language. The
  app will also inform you how much you will be paid if you complete the task
  correctly. You can withdraw from participation at any time, and you will be
  paid for the tasks you have completed till that point.
</p>
<h5>Procedure</h5>
<ol>
  <li>
    To begin, you will be introduced to the Project Coordinator for your
    location. This person will be your point of contact for help related to the
    project.
  </li>
  <li>
    Your project coordinator will provide you with instructions and if
    necessary, help you to download and install the “Karya” mobile application
    on your smartphone.
  </li>
  <li>
    Your project coordinator will give you an “Access Code”. You need to enter
    the code during the registration process. Each access code can be used only
    once. Therefore, do not share the access code with anyone else.
  </li>
  <li>
    The registration process may require you to sign-in with your phone number.
    This information will be used to identify you on the platform when you close
    the application and open it again.
  </li>
  <li>
    In addition, we will also collect some demographic information about you,
    e.g., your age range, gender, education level, etc.
  </li>
  <li>
    To receive tasks on our platform, the app must “sync” with our server. This
    operation will submit all the tasks you have completed on our platform to
    the server and receive any new tasks. After registration, the app will
    automatically sync with our server. You can trigger subsequent syncs by
    clicking on the sync button in the app.
  </li>
  <li>
    In the main app screen (dashboard), you will be presented with a list of
    different type of tasks assigned to you, along with information on each type
    of task: number of tasks assigned, number of tasks completed, number of
    tasks submitted, etc. For each type of task, the app will provide detailed
    instructions on how you must complete the task, and how much you will be
    paid if you complete the task correctly. Please pay attention to these
    instructions before proceeding with the tasks.
  </li>
  <li>
    At the end of your participation, we request you to delete the application
    from your phone. Should you want, your project coordinator will aid you in
    installing, configuring, and deleting the application.
  </li>
  <li>
    After the end of the study, we may request a short interview with you to
    gather your feedback and understand your experience of using our platform.
  </li>
</ol>
<h5>Risks and Benefits</h5>
<ol>
  <li>
    This platform only offers supplemental work. As a result, we have a limited
    number of tasks available. Do not let your participation in our platform
    interfere with your current work. Your participation will only require upto
    one to two hours of your time every day.
  </li>
  <li>
    We recommend doing the provided work in a patient manner. This will allow
    you to submit more accurate responses and will also make sure you don’t
    spend too much time on the smartphone. Spending too much time on a
    smartphone could be bad for your eyes and may affect your social life. We
    recommend not working for more than 2 hours a day.
  </li>
  <li>
    If we lend you a smartphone to participate (as part of a research study), we
    trust you to use the provided smartphone responsibly. If you have not used a
    smartphone before, it can be overwhelming. We are happy to help you in any
    and every way possible. You can contact us via your project coordinator.
  </li>
</ol>
<h5>Personal Information</h5>
<p>
  Any personal information we collect during the study will only be used to
  identify you during the duration of the study. We will delete all personal
  information as soon as the study is over. We will not share your personal
  information with anyone. However, we may use pictures from the study in
  presentations or posters without identifying specific individuals. We will
  request your permission before taking pictures and obtain your permission to
  use those pictures in our presentations or posters. Not providing consent for
  taking pictures will not disqualify you from participating in the study. For
  additional information or concerns, please contact us through your project
  coordinator.
</p>
<h5>Payment for Participation</h5>
<p>
  You will be paid for all correctly completed tasks on the platform. The app or
  your project coordinator will also provide you feedback on how well you are
  performing on the platform so that you can improve your responses for future
  tasks. We will work with you and your project coordinator to identify the best
  mode of payment. We will collect and store your payment information for the
  duration of the study. We will pay you periodically for all your tasks that
  have undergone quality verification. We will delete all payment information as
  soon as your participation is completed. Please contact your project
  coordinator if you have any queries regarding payments.
</p>
<h5>Dataset Collected from the Study</h5>
<p>
  Depending on the source of the task, we will use the dataset collected as part
  of your responses for the task for various purposes including releasing them
  publicly for research purposes. For each task, we will explain to you the end
  use of the dataset via your project coordinator. Most datasets will contain
  only text or audio data that is not associated with personally identifiable
  information. In situations where a dataset does contain personally
  identifiable information (e.g., video), we will obtain explicit consent from
  you before providing such a task. If you have any questions regarding how the
  dataset will be used, please feel free to ask us through your project
  coordinator or using the email address provided below.
</p>
<h5>Contact Information</h5>
<p>
  Should you have any questions about your participation, please contact us via
  email at thekaryainc+questions@gmail.com. In case you do not have access to
  email, you can contact your project coordinator, and have them relay your
  concerns.
</p>
<h5>Consent</h5>
<p>
  By clicking “I agree” below, you confirm that the goals and the procedure for
  participation on the platform was explained to you, you had a chance to ask
  questions before beginning your participation, and all your questions were
  answered satisfactorily. By clicking “I agree” below, you voluntarily consent
  to participate, and you do not give up any legal rights you have as a study
  participant. On behalf of Karya Inc, we thank you for your contribution and
  look forward to your participation. Do you understand and consent to these
  terms?
</p>
 ]]>
    </string>

    <!-- Phone Number -->
    <string name="phone_number_title">Phone Number</string>
    <string name="phone_number_prompt">To use Karya, you need to register with our application using your phone number. Please enter your phone number below.</string>
    <string name="unable_to_generate_otp">We could not generate an OTP for this phone number. Please check the number or try again later.</string>
    <string name="access_code_already_used">The access code is already registered to a different phone number. Please contact the coordinator for a new access code.</string>

    <!-- OTP -->
    <string name="otp_title">OTP</string>
    <string name="otp_prompt">We have sent a 6-digit OTP via SMS to 0000000000. Please enter the OTP below.</string>
    <string name="resend_otp">Resend OTP</string>
    <string name="change_phone_number">Change Phone Number</string>
    <string name="invalid_otp">You have entered an invalid OTP.</string>

    <!-- Home Screen -->
    <string name="home_screen_title">Home Screen</string>
    <string name="task_summary_label">Task Summary</string>
    <string name="click_to_do_tasks">Click Here To Do Tasks!</string>
    <string name="performance_label">Performance</string>
    <string name="recording_task_label">Recording</string>
    <string name="typing_task_label">Typing</string>
    <string name="image_task_label">Image Annotation</string>
    <string name="transcription_task_label">Transcription</string>
    <string name="earning_label">Earnings</string>
    <string name="earned_week_label">Last Week</string>
    <string name="earned_total_label">Total Earned</string>
    <string name="paid_total_label">Total Paid</string>

    <!-- Profile Screen -->
    <string name="profile_screen_title">Your Profile</string>
    <string name="submit_profile">Submit Profile</string>
    <string name="back_to_home">Back to Home</string>

    <!-- Dashboard -->
    <string name="dashboard_title">Task List</string>
    <string name="sync_prompt">Submit Tasks / Get New Tasks</string>
    <string name="tasks_available">available</string>
    <string name="tasks_completed">completed</string>
    <string name="tasks_submitted">submitted</string>
    <string name="tasks_verified">verified</string>
    <string name="tasks_skipped">skipped</string>
    <string name="tasks_expired">expired</string>
    <string name="week_label">Week</string>
    <string name="day_label">Day</string>

    <!-- Leaderboard -->
    <string name="leaderboard_title">Leaderboard</string>
    <string name="leaderboard_points">points</string>
    <string name="leaderboard_empty">There is no one on the leaderboard now. Complete tasks and be the first to get on the leaderboard!</string>


    <string name="sync_prompt_message">You have completed tasks that can be submitted to the server. Do you want to submit the tasks now?</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>

    <string name="task_outside_time_bound">You can do this task only between _START_TIME_ and _END_TIME_.</string>
    <string name="okay">Okay</string>

    <!-- Sync -->
    <string name="reset_assignment_warning">Some output files were missing.</string>
    <string name="upload_file_error">Error while uploading files. Please contact your coordinator.</string>
    <string name="send_db_error">Error while sending tasks. Please contact your coordinator.</string>
    <string name="receive_db_error">Error while receiving tasks. Please contact your coordinator.</string>
    <string name="download_file_error">Error while downloading files. Please contact your coordinator.</string>
    <string name="received_verified_error">Error while receiving validations. Please contact your coordinator.</string>

    <!-- Payment screens -->


    <string name="payment_transferred">Transferred</string>
    <string name="rs_float">₹%.2f</string>
    <string name="balance">Balance</string>
    <string name="all_transactions">All Transactions</string>
    <string name="account_details">Account Details</string>
    <string name="payment_dashboard_title">Payment Dashboard</string>
    <string name="payment_mode">Payment Mode</string>
    <string name="account_id_label">Account ID</string>
    <string name="update_account_details">Update Account Details</string>


    <string name="payment_account_holder_name_hint">Name</string>
    <string name="ifsc_code_hint">IFSC Code</string>
    <string name="account_number_hint">Account Number</string>
    <string name="re_enter_account_number">Re-enter Account Number</string>
    <string name="payment_registration_submit">Submit</string>

    <string name="payment_registration_upi_hint">UPI ID</string>
    <string name="re_enter_upi_id">Re-enter UPI ID</string>

    <string name="payment_registration_failure_message">We were not able to register your account with the given details.</string>
    <string name="register_account_again">Register account again</string>
    <string name="payment_contact_project_coordinator_message">contact project coordinator</string>

    <string name="payment_registration_title">Payment Registration</string>
    <string name="bank_account_label">Bank Account Number</string>
    <string name="upi_label">UPI</string>

    <string name="payment_registration_description">Do you want to get paid via your bank account or your UPI ID?</string>
    <string name="bank_account_details_title">Bank Account Details</string>
    <string name="upi_details_title">UPI Details</string>

    <string name="payment_info_verification_title">Account Verification</string>
    <string name="verification_request_processing">We are checking your payment information. Please check again in a few hours. If you still see this message one day after submitting your payment information, contact your coordinator.</string>
    <string name="verification_request_processed">To verify your payment information, we have sent you ₹2. Please confirm if you have received the amount by clicking the appropriate button.</string>
    <string name="verification_loading">Checking the status of your payment verification. Please wait.</string>
    <string name="received_verification_amount">Yes. I have received ₹2 in my account</string>
    <string name="not_received_verification_amount">No. I have not received ₹2 in my account</string>

    <!-- Speech verification strings -->
    <string name="speech_verification_instruction">Verify the recording below</string>
    <string name="recording_accuracy">Accuracy</string>
    <string name="accuracy_good">Correct</string>
    <string name="accuracy_okay">Errors</string>
    <string name="accuracy_bad">Incorrect</string>
    <string name="recording_volume">Volume</string>
    <string name="volume_good">Good</string>
    <string name="volume_okay">Whisper</string>
    <string name="volume_bad">Inaudible</string>
    <string name="recording_quality">Quality</string>
    <string name="recording_noise">Noise</string>
    <string name="quality_good">Good</string>
    <string name="quality_okay">Noisy</string>
    <string name="quality_bad">Bad</string>
    <string name="recording_fluency">Fluency</string>
    <string name="fluency_good">Fluent</string>
    <string name="fluency_okay">Okay</string>
    <string name="fluency_bad">Broken</string>
    <string name="rating_undefined">Undefined</string>
    <string name="corrupt_audio_file_message">Audio file is corrupt</string>

    <string name="app_name">Karya</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>

    <!-- Transliteration strings -->
    <string name="transliteration_hint">Start Typing…</string>
    <string name="text_transliteration_desc">Please transliterate the following word from English to Hindi</string>
    <string name="alphanumericString">abcdefghijklmnopqrstuvwxyz</string>

    <!-- Speech recording strings -->
    <string name="speech_recording_instruction">Record the sentence below</string>

    <!-- Image transcription strings -->
    <string name="image_transcription_instruction">Type what you see in the image below</string>

    <!-- Image labelling string -->
    <string name="image_labelling_instruction">Label the images below</string>

    <!-- Image data collection strings -->
    <string name="image_data_collection_instruction">Take a picture of the front cover. Move to a random page. Take pictures of # continuous pages from the random page</string>

    <!-- Image annotation strings -->
    <string name="image_annotation_instruction">Annotation instruction goes here</string>

    <!-- Sentence validation strings -->
    <string name="sentence_validation_instruction">Is the sentence below correct?</string>
    <string name="grammar_question">Is the above sentence grammatically correct?</string>
    <string name="spelling_question">Are all the words spelt correctly in the sentence?</string>

    <!-- Sign verification strings -->
    <string name="video_good">Good</string>
    <string name="video_average">Average</string>
    <string name="video_poor">Poor</string>

    <!-- Image alt texts -->
    <string name="karya_logo">Project Karya Logo</string>
    <string name="next">next</string>
    <string name="replay">replay</string>
    <string name="back">back</string>
    <string name="skip_task_warning">Are you sure you want to skip the task?</string>
    <string name="no_transcription_error_msg">Please enter the transcription</string>
    <string name="speech_transcription_instruction">Transcribe the audio below</string>
    <string name="proceed_text">Proceed</string>
    <string name="cancel_text">Cancel</string>
    <string name="no_annotation_box_dialog_title_text">No Box Drawn</string>
    <string name="no_annotation_box_annotation_message_text">No boxes are drawn to the screen. Do you want to proceed?</string>
    <string name="select_image_annotation_label_dialog_instruction">Select Label</string>
    <string name="image_annotation_edit_label">Select new label</string>
    <string name="profile_picture">profile picture</string>
    <string name="rotate_right">rotate</string>

    <string name="no_internet">No internet available</string>
    <string name="image_annotation_verification_instruction">Verification instruction goes here</string>
    <string name="img_annotation_verification_good">good</string>
    <string name="img_annotation_verification_ok">ok</string>
    <string name="img_annotation_verification_bad">bad</string>
    <string name="no_image_validation_score_selected">Please select a score for the annotation</string>
    <string name="sentence_corpus_verification_valid">VALID</string>
    <string name="sentence_corpus_verification_errors">ERRORS</string>
    <string name="sentence_corpus_verification_invalid">INVALID</string>
    <string name="profile_name_label">Name</string>
    <string name="profile_gender_label">Gender</string>
    <string name="profile_yob_label">Year Of Birth</string>
    <string name="profile_missing_field_error_msg">Please fill all the fields</string>
    <string name="profile_gender_male_label">Male</string>
    <string name="profile_gender_female_label">Female</string>

    <!-- Holiday Message -->
    <string name="sunday_message">Today is Sunday. Take the day off!</string>
    <string name="diwali_message">Happy Diwali! Enjoy the break. You can start work again on Thursday!</string>
</resources>
